

JAKE ECKHARDT

web developer

jake.c.eckhardt@gmail.com

💂 jakeckhardt-portfolio.vercel.app

217.710.9937

St. Louis, MO.

I am a driven and innovative web developer with five years experience creating user-friendly web interfaces, implementing Content Management Systems, and delighting customers with dazzling E-Commerce solutions, known for my problem-solving abilities and commitment and continuous learning.

SKILLS

JavaScript NodeJS
ReactJS NextJS

Svelte CSS/SASS

Tailwind CSS Responsive Design

UX/UI MongoDB

REST APIs PostgreSQL

Agile Git



EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Front-end Developer

Anheuser-Busch - St. Louis, MO. June 2019 - Present
Development of user-facing features using modern web
technologies such as Node.js, Svelte, SASS, and ReactJS to create
intuitive interfaces for AB-specific products. Collaborated with
designers and worked with brands like Budweiser, Michelob Ultra,
and Stella to develop engaging websites and custom applications.

Front-end Developer

Upland Second Street- St. Louis, MO.

Nov. 2019 - Nov. 2020

Development of multiple customer creation promotion platforms

using Ember.js and CSS. I focused on enhancing user engagement
and streamlining the promotion process while collaborating with

cross-functional teams to meet business requirements.

Web Master

375th AMW Public Affairs - Scott AFB, IL. May 2011 - Oct. 2016 Management of the official Scott AFB website using Armed Forces Public Information Management System CMS, HTML, CSS, and JavaScript. Achieved recognition as the Air Force Website of the Year in 2011 for outstanding design and functionality.



EDUCATION

Certificate: LC101

LaunchCode - Seattle, WA. May 2016 - Nov. 2016

Certificate: Digital Multimedia

Defense Information School - Fort Meade, MA. May 2015 - July 2015



ACCOMPLISHMENTS

- Lead the transition of multiple newly acquired brand sites to the Svelte tech stack.
- Learned multiple languages and systems, such as AEM, Drupal, Ember.js, Hugo, Svelte, Liquid, and React.js to help team across multiple platforms.
- Implemented an E-Commerce solution lowering the abandoned cart rate to 60% - 10% lower than the average.